[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":37022,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":318253,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7134,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":325389,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":9104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":334493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1519,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":336013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6320,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":342333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":54607,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":396941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the secon d one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":401861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":856,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":402717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2632,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":405349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1144,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":406493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2600,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":409093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6 </sub> 0  = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":791,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":409885,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":412309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":952,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":413261,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><b r /> (Re member, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":1520,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":414781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":727,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":415508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. )","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2304,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":417813,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":766,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":418581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":1528,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":420109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":624,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":420733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":1752,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":422485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":807,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":423292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":13343,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":436637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse un der +<su b>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":15680,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":452318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":9559,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":461877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1264,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":463141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br />  (Rememb er, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":465997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":662,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":466660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":469445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":703,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":470149,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2448,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":472598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6< /sub>.","rt":694,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":473293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":1984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":475277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3032,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":478309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be perfo rmed sta rting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":5392,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":483701,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but th ere is n o way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":42648,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":526349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":530797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1071,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":531869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember,  a gener ator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2480,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":534349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":14319,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":548669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br  /> (Rem ember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":551229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":896,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":552125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":1896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":554021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":960,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":554981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question  with fe edback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":6632,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":561613,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2776,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":564389,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":808,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":565197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":1984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":567181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":8450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":575631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5854,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":581486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":1462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":582949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4391,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":587341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":4992,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":592333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"I added 4 and 1 together to get 5. Saw that 5 is below the number 9 and that is my answer.","explanation_history":["I ha","I h","I added 4 and 1 together to get 5. Saw that 5 is below the number 9 and that is my answer."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":25952,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":618285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is bigger than 9 so I subtracted to get 3.","explanation_history":["Added 8 to 4 to get 12. !2","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. !","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is bett","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is  bet","A dded 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is be","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is bigger than 9 so i su","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is bigger than 9 so i s","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is bigger than 9 so i ","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is bigger than 9 so i","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is bigger than 9 so I subr","Added 8 to 4 to get 12. 12 is bigger than 9 so I subtracted to get 3."],"response_history":["12","1","3"],"rt":34688,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":652973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":true,"explanation":"9 and 9 are the same.","explanation_history":["( a","( ","(","9 and 0","9 and 9 are the same."],"response_history":["9"],"rt":14215,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":667189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 2-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":9896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":677085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":4224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":681309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":683989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"3 plus 6 equals 9","explanation_history":["#","3 plus 6 ea","3 plus 6 equals 9"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":14550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":698540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't know.","explanation_history":["i ","i","I don't know."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":13152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":711692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a  generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"3 is a multiple of 9","explanation_history":["3 is a multiple of 9"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":9783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":721476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"5 is not a multiple of 9","explanation_history":["5 is not a multpl","5 is not a multp","5 is not a multiple o f","5 is not a multiple o ","5 is not a multiple of 9"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":9648,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":731124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is  6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"6 is a multiple of 3","explanation_history":["d","6 is a multiple of 3"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":12575,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":743700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":7721,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":751421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub> ?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":755485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't understand.","explanation_history":["i ","i","I don't understand."],"response_history":["x"],"rt":26207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":781693,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm completely confused","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Im","I'm completely confused"],"rt":11503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":793197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":4928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":798125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":1495,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":799621,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":1487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":801109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't know.","explanation_history":["I don't know."],"response_history":["True"],"rt":6119,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":807229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":2711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":809941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't know.","explanation_history":["I don't know."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":3375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":813317,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":1608,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":814925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1808,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":816733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free ","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"23","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["23"],"rt":2567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":819301,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2648,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":821949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list the m.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"stats","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["stats"],"rt":8711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":830661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3864,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":834525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi ","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently","3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":20728,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":855253,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3816,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":859069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do  you feel  you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2672,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":861741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":864661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":2016,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":866677,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":4808,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":871485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":3641,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":875126,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any com ments on  this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"none","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["none"],"rt":2703,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":877829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]